<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Windows on Arto&#39;s dev time by-products</title>
    <link>https://artosalminen.github.io/series/windows/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Windows on Arto&#39;s dev time by-products</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://artosalminen.github.io/series/windows/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to Download Streaming Video Using ffmpeg</title>
      <link>https://artosalminen.github.io/posts/how-to-download-streaming-video-with-ffmpeg/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://artosalminen.github.io/posts/how-to-download-streaming-video-with-ffmpeg/</guid>
      <description>How to Download Streaming Video Using ffmpeg Streaming video has become ubiquitous, but sometimes you might want to save a portion of a video for offline viewing or archival purposes. One powerful tool for this task is ffmpeg, a versatile command-line program for handling multimedia data. In this guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll walk you through the process of installing ffmpeg and using it to download streaming video.
Installing ffmpeg Before you can use ffmpeg, you need to install it on your system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to resolve Intel Graphics Command Center port conflict</title>
      <link>https://artosalminen.github.io/posts/how-to-resolve-intel-control-center-port-conflict/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://artosalminen.github.io/posts/how-to-resolve-intel-control-center-port-conflict/</guid>
      <description>For developers working on .NET Core and other development servers, encountering port conflicts can be a common issue. Recently, I came accross with the default port (5000) used for local development server and the Intel(R) Graphics Command Center server. In this blog post, I&amp;rsquo;ll introduce a workaround that involves editing the Windows registry to resolve the conflict and ensure smooth development processes.
Understanding the Issue:
The Intel(R) Graphics Command Center server, specifically the OneApp.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
